Hey guys, welcome to another video, I hope enjoyed you have enjoyed the previous video
which I have explained the Microsoft Defender ATP, talked about on this, how the ADR
will basically work, you have seen everything, I hope, let's talk about the DLP which will
be used in most of the organization, so DLP is like a data last prevention, you can see
the protection name in the word data last protection, so this tool will basically, we can
stop the exfiltration by using this tool, so if any of the data get uploaded from the
company to the cloud to the detector will pay web server or anything, the DLP will be coming
to actions, it will be blocked that traffic and it will send a lot to the administrator
like an ADR, basically we can integrate that also, to ADLP, so basically this DLP will
filter all the, it will basically it will monitor all the network traffic on by one, so it
will take one packet and it will investigate what was sending and what was what how
many byte was sending and how many bytes are receiving and which IP, whether the IP has
any reputations or not and it will decide whether the, whether any of the data will be
exfiltered from the company that uploaded from the company or any of the malicious connections
where they are, this will basically stop that exfiltration and to the, from the organization,
okay, so the data loss protection prevention or protection you can whatever is possible,
you can say that, this mechanism have a capability to detect this kind of security breach,
particularly the data exfiltration, okay, so let us go up of this video and we will continue
the discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye bye.